九叔
Jiushu
三婶，早
Aunt, early
早，你方便啊
Early, convenient for you ah
生意好吧
Well business
石头，剪刀，布
Rock, scissors, cloth
就会欺负我
Would bully me
师妹，你知不知道师父去了哪里？
Junior sister apprentice, you know master gone?
我怎么知道啊
How do I know ah
那你惨了，我要你背我找到师父为止
Then you miserable, I want you back I find the master so far
你有没有搞错？ 我整间酒厂才值五千块钱？
Are you crazy? I just value the whole winery five thousand dollars?
像你这样漫天杀价 当心你以后生儿子没屁眼
Like you did not bargain Beware days after you son did asshole
我是在商言商，而且你这间厂不干净
I am a business is business, and you is not clean that plant
卖不卖，你自己拿主意了
You serve your own mind
你不要听人瞎册，说我这间酒厂有鬼
Do not listen to people in vain, that I was something fishy this winery
像你这样喝过洋墨水的人 怎么也会相信鬼呢？
Like you who drink ocean ink how it will believe in ghosts?
信不信在我，有没有 鬼呢，大家都知道
Believe me, there is no ghost it, we all know
不然的话
Otherwise
像你这样的铁公鸡， 怎么会急着脱手呢？
Stingy like you, how will be anxious to get rid of it?
好，算你狠，你是落井下石趁火打劫
Well, count you vicious, you are adding insult to injury looting
就算有鬼，我也没怕过
Even ghosts, I did not afraid
九叔早，喝早茶啊
Jiushu early morning tea ah
阿九
A nine
你应该叫他九叔才对哦
You should call him, oh Jiushu fishes
九叔？
Jiushu?
你别看我比他年轻， 我的辈分可比他大
Even though I'm younger than him I like him big generational
我今天心情好，才叫他阿九
Today I feel good, called him A nine
要是我心情不好，我就叫他狗蛋
If I feel bad, I called him a dog egg
师父
Master
你们两个在干什么？
What are you two doing?
师兄脚痛
Brother hurts
是啊，我脚痛
Yes ah, I podiatry
都是你
Are you
什么啊
What ah
阿九，阿九，阿九
A nine, A nine, A nine
阿九，阿九
A nine, A nine
伙计，帮我沏壶龙并
Dude, help me to brew a pot Longjing
你聋着，你没听到九叔叫龙并啊
Are you deaf, ah, you did not hear Jiushu called Longjing ah
来了
Come
九叔，我有件事想挑你发财
Jiushu, I have something you want to pick a fortune
多谢了，我没有这福份
Thank you, I do not have good fortune
你也知道，这件事对你 来说是轻而易举的0麻
You know, it is easy for you Well
对你，我就不举
For you, I will not give
九叔，这价钱由你开，您 开得出，我就付得起
Jiushu, that the price to you to open, you open the draw, I can afford
我老实告诉你，你做了那么多缺德事
I honestly tell you that you have done so much wicked things
就算抓到了鬼，你也不好过
Even caught a ghost, you are not better
不如留着钱，买块好坟地吧
Better to keep the money, buy a piece of good bars cemetery
你
You
我照事实说
I did say the fact that
大小姐回来了
Missy back
多谢
Thank you
老板，你别走啊，有的谈，有的谈
Boss, you do not go. Ah, some talk, some talk
欢迎回家，我好想你哦
Welcome home, I miss you oh
我也是
I am also
玩得开心吗？
Have fun?
很开心
Very happy
真的？国外的生活你还习惯吗？
Really? Living abroad habits do you have?
一定有好多好玩的事，说来听听
Fixed a lot of fun things, said to listen to
好啊，好多事情都好好玩，好好笑哦
Good. Ah, a lot of things are good fun, a good laugh, oh
你想干什么
What do you want
帮你买火柴
Help you buy matches
不用了，我戒烟了
No, I quit smoking
去买包火柴
Buy a pack of matches
既然你对附近很熟，那我就麻烦你了
Since you are very familiar with the vicinity, I'll trouble you
他是说，今天晚上想请我们吃晚饭
He said that today would like to invite us to dinner at night
对，接风，吃晚饭
Right, Jie Feng, dinner
祠堂还有点事，帮我包点东西回去
Shrine have something to help me pack something back
师兄
Brother
随便包两个包给师父吃就行了
Just pack two contracted Master eat on the line
你还记不记得我？
Do you remember me?
小时候跟你一起玩的阿星，小星星
Child playing with you A star, little star
他说什么？
What did he say?
你不懂的
You do not understand
我们到楼上谈
We went upstairs to talk
师兄，他们笑你什么啊？
Brothers, they laugh at you what ah?
他们笑我什么都不懂
They laugh at me do not understand anything
他们笑得对呀
They laughed Yes
但我懂得抓鬼呀
But I know how to catch Guiya
你敢吗？
You dare to do?
不敢
Dare
好了，不要唉声叹气了
Well, do not moan and groan a
赵太公，驱魔斩妖我师父拿手
Zhaotai Gong, my master good demon exorcism
抓鬼除邪我师兄也会哦
Chan evil ghosts, oh my brothers would
就凭他？
Relying on him?
就凭我？
Relying on me?
我师父会的我也会
I will I will master
我师父不会的，我一样也会
My master will not, like me, will
这样子啦，我们算你 少一点，五百大洋
This way again, and we count you a little less, five hundred oceans
五百
Five hundred
十块
Ten
成了
Became
怎么样？
How about?
你小心，乱杀价，生儿子没屁眼
You be careful, chaotic bargain, no asshole son
你
You. . .
一定要这么大的排场吗？
Scheduled to do so much pomp?
我收你的钱，当然要摆 个大排场给你看看了
I received your preserves, of course, put a big show for you to see the
我现在要起坛跟鬼谈判 ，谈的拢嘛，是你幸运
I now want to negotiate with the ghost from the altar, to talk about rope Well, are you lucky
那如果谈不拢呢？
If unable to agree that it?
那就要起坛做法，难 度很高，要加钱的哦
It would have to approach from the altar, very difficult, and to raise money, oh
喂，大姐！
Hello, Sister!
不是大姐，是抓鬼大师
Not Sister, is master of ghosts
好，大师，我们不是说好 了吗？这戏要做全套的
Well, Master, we are not saying that good? Do this drama full
你们这一会儿你又加钱了呢，我
It also added you money while you do for me. . .
师兄，你听到了
Brother, did you hear
听到了
Heard
如果谈不拢我们就收拾东西 走了，反正死也是死别人
Failing an agreement, we pack up and go, anyway, someone dead is dead
我给，我给，钱嘛，好说好说
I end, I knot, money Well, Say say
你看着
You look at
阎王坐山
Yama mountain ride
小鬼引路
Imp lead the way
洒冥钱
Sprinkle offerings of money
洒，我洒
Sprinkle, sprinkle me
招魂现身
Evocation appeared
上剑
The sword
雪花盖顶
Ray Flowers roof
枯树盘根
Withered packing
观音坐莲
Buddha sitting on lotus
嫦娥奔月
Moon
师兄，念回魂经
Brother, read Huihun by
念
Study
怎么念？
How to read?
自己篇
Own
敲鬼门关
Knock on the gates of hell
再诉心中情，再敲鬼门关
Whispers again, then knock the gates of hell
三叩鬼门关
Three knock jaws
继续往下演
Continue down the speech
不要停
Do not stop
上身
Upper body
继续做戏
Continue to put on a show
来者何人，报上名来
Who goes, Newspaper name
李氏小红
Lee red
为何阴魂不散苦苦纠缠
Why lingering bitter divisions entanglement
我怎么回答你呀
How do I answer you die
你若有难言之隐，不 用怕，尽管道出来
Are you hiding something bitter, do not be afraid, though road out
我道不出来，出点是非题吧
I said do not come out, the point of a non-title bar
李氏，是不是有冤情？
Lee is not a grievance?
是呀，我死得好冤枉啊
Yes, I riddance wronged ah
你死的不甘心啊？
Are you willing to die ah?
是
好，你把你的身世说给我听
Well, you put your life experience tell me
我说出来，你们一定不相信
I say it, you must not believe
从我十二岁开始，就失身给他
From the beginning I was twelve years old, you lose your virginity to him
禽兽
Bestial
我父母找他理论，谁知被他杀了
I try to find his father theory, who knows were killed
还长期的占有我
I am also a long-term possession
真是没有人性
Really no humanity
到我十五岁的时候，他又另结新欢
To when I was fifteen, he Lingjiexinhuan
于是设计人轮奸我
So design raped me
可恶，简直不是人
Damn, people are simply not
还诬陷我与人通奸
I have also framed with adultery
藉口活活把我淹死，我死得好冤啊
Excuse me alive to drown, I riddance injustice ah
你编的是不是太离谱了，鬼才全你呢
You are not too high spectral series, the devil letter How about you
你还找人整我？
You have to find someone to fix me?
不关我事啊
Not my thing ah
走啊
Walked
不关我们的事
Not our thing
你们有没有收他的钱
You have not received his money
没
Not
有啊有啊
There have ah ah
你们要打散我的魂，我就要你们的命
You want to break up my soul, my life would you
不要
Must not
金蝉脱壳
Withdraw its role
快收拾东西，走人啊
Quickly pack up, leave ah
不要抓我啊，不关我的事啊
Do not catch me, ah, ah not my thing
天地无心，乾坤定
Centerless world, heaven and earth fixed
晕了晕了
Halo halo
没事，怎么会这样呢
Nothing, how could this happen
看本少爷斩妖除魔
See the young master demon slayer
符呢？
Breaks it?
看你往哪儿跑
See you where to run
今天豁出去了
Today fight it
我跟你拼了
I fight with you
你干什么
What are you doing
你脱我裤子干什么？你好色哟
You take off my pants doing? Your lust yo
你别走嘛
Do not go bowel
我又晕了
I was dizzy
我搞什么鬼啊
I hell ah
师父
Master
阿星呢
A sing it
师兄被女鬼抓到棺材 里了，快点救他啊
Brothers were caught ghost coffin, hurry to save him ah
师父，打不开啊， 怎么办，快点救他嘛
Master, open ah, how to do, come to save him Well
让开
Step aside
鬼上身
Troublesome
有符了，有符了
There are characters, and there are symbols of the
你们两个好大的胆子
How dare you two
不关我事啊，是师妹
Not my thing, ah, junior sister apprentice
不是我，我跟师兄说过 ，要先告诉师父的嘛
Not me, I told Brother said, first thing to tell Master
快点收拾家伙
Come pick up guys
天灵灵，地灵灵， 湘西赶尸，生人回避
Day Lingling Lingling, Hunan Vampire, avoiding strangers
教堂重开了，教堂重开了
Reopened the church, the church reopened
阿星，阿星
A Star, A Star
小月！小月
Satsuki. . . Satsuki
我今天奉万能的主，再次来到这里
Today, I serve the Almighty, here again
带领你们脱离罪恶
Lead you from sin
这个世界太恐怖了
The world is too scary
朋友不信朋友，亲戚 不信亲戚，人不信人
Friends do not believe in friends, relatives do not believe relatives, people who do not believe
所以你们要相信我，因我是天父之子
So you have to believe me, because I was the son of the Father
只要相信我，你们将成为天父的儿女
Just trust me, you will become the sons and daughters of the Father
别抢别抢
Do not rush to grab
上主，没有你仁慈的助 佑，我们便一无所有
Lord, do not you kind help of Mary, we have nothing
求你原谅我卑微的礼品和祈祷
Ask you to forgive my humble gifts and prayers
恩赐我们行善的力量
Gift of our force for good
你们要有信心，要虔诚，要奉献
You must have faith, to piety, devotion to
愿主与我们同在
May the Lord be with us in
因父、及子及圣神之名者，阿门
Father, Son and Holy Spirit in the name of those who, Amen
来来来，行善最乐，我 们大家一起来捐献
Come, come, do good morning music, all of us together to donate
行善是最快乐的事了
King is happy to do good things
谢谢你
Thank you
师兄，师兄
Brother, Brother
我来奉献的
I'll sacrifice
爹地，你都捐献啊
Daddy, you donate ah
好
Good
这一下亏大了
This is about a big loss
借点钱给我
I borrowed some money knot
不要
Must not
我连上次的一起还给你
I could not even pay you back together last
不借
Loaned
我连上次借的双倍还给你，好不好？
I could not even last through the double back to you, okay?
好，一定哦
Well, sure, oh
当然了
Of course
不准撒赖
Allowed Salai
爹地，谢谢你
Daddy, thank you
万能的主啊，我要奉献啊
Almighty God. Ah, I want to dedicate ah
师父来了
Master came
不用抢不用抢，人人有份的
Do not rush to grab, for everyone's
你们干什么？
What are you doing?
教堂不可以重开的
The church can not be re-opened
你们是什么人
What are you people
对不起，我是吴修士，从凡帝岗来的
Sorry, I was Wuxiu Shi, come from where DKI
我只听过景阳岗，卧龙 岗，没听过什么凡帝岗
I only heard Jingyang Gang, Wollongong, heard what Where DKI
神父，这位是九叔
Father, this is Jiushu
九叔
Jiushu
死不死是你家的事
Sibu Si is a matter of your home
如果你开了这个门，大家都会死
If you opened the door, everyone will die
为什么？
Why?
你知不知道这个是什么位？
Do you know what this is bit?
门口位
Door position
这是酒泉镇最邪的三煞位
This is the most evil of the town of Jiuquan three evil bit
三煞位？
Three evil place?
什么叫做三煞位？
What is called the three evil place?
三煞位的英文叫Three powr
Three evil bit of English called Three powr
Three powr
我不管你们打什么炮 ，反正这里就不能开
I do not care what you ordered guns, anyway here it can not be opened
开了之后，全镇就会鸡犬不宁
After the opening, the town will utter confusion
如果是鸡犬不灵，那没关系
If it is just a few kilometers ineffective, it does not matter
天主赐福世人，人没事就好了
God bless the people of the world, nothing like a man
我警告你，这个门一 开，随时都会死人
I warn you, this door - open, at any time the dead
到时候谁负责
Who is responsible for that time
我负责
I am responsible for
你负责？
You are responsible for '
我负责做弥撒
I am responsible for doing mass
好了，你告诉我，谁叫你重开教堂的
Well, you tell me who told you to reopen the church
奉天主之命
Mukden Lord of life
天主？
God?
MY GOD
卖狗的，你是说街上 那个卖狗的癫痢头？
Sell ??dogs, you're saying on the street that sell dog Laili Tou?
他有权叫你重开教堂？
He is entitled to ask you to re-open the church?
九叔，My God 是天主的意思
Jiushu, MyGod is the meaning of God
我不管什么卖狗的卖猫 的，反正教堂不能开
I do not care what the selling dogs to sell cats, anyway, the church can not be opened
愿天主宽恕你的罪
May God forgive your sins
你想和我动手？
Do you want hands-on?
九叔，这里是公家的地方
Jiushu, here is the public place
神父要重开教堂，你不肯
To re-open the church priest, you do not aim
我们找镇长来主持公 道，你看怎么样？
We look for the mayor to justice, you see how?
好
Good
各位乡亲父老，叔伯兄弟
My fellow elders, brothers and uncles
我身为酒泉镇一镇之长
I, as the head of the Jiuquan town, a town
有责任维护酒泉镇的繁荣和安定
Are responsible for maintaining the prosperity and stability of the town of Jiuquan
不过，现在发生重大的问题
Now, however, a major problem
所以请大家到这来， 一起解决中西的问题
So let us come to this, - from West to solve the problems
西洋有许多先进的东 西，像是大飞机
Western has many advanced things, like large aircraft ...
打字机
Typewriter
打字机，还有很多，什 么蒸气机，录音机
Typewriters, there are many, what steam engine, the recorder
现在流行的就是搞飞机啊
Now popular is to engage aircraft ah
中国的传统我们可以继续的发扬
Chinese tradition we can continue to carry forward
像什么中国的国粹一打麻将啦
Like what the quintessence of China - play mahjong friends
充分做到了寓教于乐的功能
Fully achieve the entertaining features
激发每个人的智力
Stimulate everyone's intelligence
而且，可以达到货币流通的目的
Moreover, you can achieve the purpose of currency in circulation
间接促进了社会的繁荣
Indirectly promote the prosperity of society
繁荣之后，每个人都有钱
After the boom, everyone money
有钱就可以娶小老婆了
Money can marry his mistress.
我扯太远了
I have gone too far
其实天主教有个天主，道教有个天师
In fact, there is a God Catholicism, Taoism has a Fearless
大家都有个天，对不对？
Everyone has a day, right?
都是劝人向善，当初 道教、佛教没有人信
Are advising people to perform good deeds, had Taoism, Buddhism, no one would believe
可是时间久了，大家不 也就信了，对不对？
But over time, we do not believe it, right?
所以呢，根据我儿子这张纸的意思
So, according to my son the meaning of this piece of paper
你自己的意思
Your own meaning
是我自己的意思，我主张教堂要重开
Is my own will, I advocate the church to re-open
教堂重开呢，大家都有好处
Church re-opened it, good for everyone
又有衣服领
There clothes collar
还有牛油，奶粉，饼干，糖果可以拿
There butter, milk powder, biscuits, candy can take
只要教堂一开，大家跟着发财
As long as the church opened, we follow the fortune
现在大家举布条来表决
Now we give the cloth to vote
我们反对
We oppose
不是你们，是你
Not you, that you
阿星
A Star
你们这些杂碎，我懒得理你们了
You guys, I'm too lazy you a
九叔
Jiushu
卖菜哦，九叔，你又去方便了？
Vegetables Oh, Jiushu, you went convenient?
九叔，对不起，你也信教啊
Jiushu, I'm sorry, you believers ah
信什么教？
What religion?
上面的窗上点油
Above the window on the point of oil
神父，恭喜了
Father, congratulations
村民大会决定了，教堂可以重开了
Villagers Assembly decided, the church can be reopened
太好了，去把门打开
Great, go open the door
是，神父
Yes, Father
发财了，发财了
Fortune, fortune
阿月，我们发财了
A month, we make a fortune
想不到信天主可以得到这么多好处
Think of the letter God can get so many benefits
怪不得这么多人信天主
No wonder so many people believe in God
对啊
For ah
以后不用买衣服了
Did not have to buy clothes
师兄，这是什么东西？
Brother, what is this thing?
我也不知道，可以去AN丫
I do not know, you can go to ANY
她从国外回来，一定知道这是什么
She returned from abroad, must know what it is
干嘛要去问她？这一 看就知道是什么了嘛
Dry shun going to ask her? This look will know what it is incorrect
你确定这是用来绑头吗？
Are you sure this is used to tie the head do?
你没看过东洋浪人 用布条绑头的吗？
You have not seen Japan ronin head with a cloth tied to it?
但这个好像不同，是从西洋来的
But this seems different from the western to the
哎呀，东洋西洋，都是一个洋
Ah, western Japan, is a foreign
哦，我明白了
Oh, I understand
眼罩啊
Goggles ah
太大了
Too
我知道了
I know
原来是西洋胆兜，你穿一家好看
Original Western apron you wear some nice
可以吗？
Can you?
你穿穿看嘛，快去呀
You Chuan Chuan Kan Ma, go ah
师兄，你看，是不是这个样子
Brother, you see, is not like this
真的好看耶，难怪ANN丫那么吸引我
Really nice yeah, no wonder ANNY attracted me so much
你又提她？
You also mentioned her?
好好，不提
Well, not to mention
你要每天都穿着它，一定很好看
You have to wear it every day, we must look good
师父，你回来了？
Master, you're back?
干嘛那么急呀
Dry bowel then Jiya
女大十八变，才一夜 的功夫，就这么大了
Womanhood, was a night of martial arts, it's that big
师兄，你的头
Brother, your head
阿星
A Star
来了
Come
师父，喝茶
Master, tea
人已经长大了，衣服也不合身了
People have grown up, clothes do not fit the
这两块钱拿去买新衣服
Two dollars instead of buying new clothes
师父，那我呢
Master, what about me
你的不合身吗？
You do not fit?
平时没什么，就是早上起 来的时候，裤档老顶着
Usually no, that morning, when the old wore crotch
我也是啊
I am also ah
你也会啊
You will also ah
那是什么
What is it
阁楼板
Loft board
我说的是这个
I said that this
师父，我知道了
Master, I know
那是师兄从教堂拿回来的头带
That's brothers from the church to take back headband
我刚刚从师兄通过教堂
I just returned from brothers through the church
看到有一大堆人在听 一个修士胡说八道
See that there are a lot of people listening to a monk nonsense
我叫师兄不要听 我还说师父知道了一点会骂的
I'm not listening to my brothers said master will know a little cursing
师兄又不听我劝
I would advise not to listen brothers
这是什么？
What is it?
这是教会送的西洋内裤 ，还有西洋肚兜在里面
This is the Western church to send underwear, as well as western apron on the inside
拿来
Bring
两块钱
Two dollars
阿星，小月
A star, Satsuki
师父，什么事
Master, what
没听什么声音吗？拿家伙
What is the sound you heard? Take guys
神父来了
Father came
神父，欢迎
Father, please
不好意思不好意思
Sorry sorry
各位，神父就不用我介绍了
Ladies and gentlemen, I would not have introduced Father
坐，坐
Sit, sit
神父，这位是ANN丫，ANN丫 的父亲是酒楼的老板
Father, this is ANNY, ANNY's father was the boss of the restaurant
这位董先生也是如意赌坊的老板
Mr. Tong is also the owner of wishful Dufang
赌坊？
Dufang?
就是CLUB
Is the CLUB
哦，CLUB
Oh, CLUB
这位是云仙烟馆的李掌柜的
This is Unzen dens Lee dispensers
云仙烟馆是
Unzen dens yes. . .
Smoka
Smoke
Smoka，我知道
Smoke, I know
这两位是凤凰楼的老板娘
These two are the boss Phoenix House
凤凰楼是什么？
Phoenix House is what?
Chiken
chiken
鸡馆，我知道了，就是可 以吃的鸡，对不对？
Chicken house, I know, is that you can eat chicken, right?
对
To
我喜欢吃鸡
I laugh chicken
她们的鸡一定很好吃哦
They must be good to eat Oh chicken
是呀，改天我们可以到她们那儿去 尝尝她们的鸡
Star Yeah, another day to go to them we can try their chicken
可以吧？
Can it?
奇怪，怎么九叔还没来呢？
Strange, how Jiushu not come yet?
我想他应该就快到了
I think he should be just around the corner
走
师父，有免费的吃，为什么走啊
Master, there is free food, why walked
是啊是啊，师父，都已经 来了，为什么不上去？
Yes ah yes ah, Master, have come, why do not you go?
是不是怕他？
Is not afraid of him?
谁怕他？回去
Who is afraid of him? Back
为什么要走呢，师父
Why leave it, Master
你没看见那个天师，他 摆好架势，穿好袍服
Can not you see that Fearless, he gracefully posture, dress robes
你看看我像什么样子，回去
You see what I'm like, go back
九叔到
Jiushu to
九叔，欢迎，欢迎，来
Jiushu, welcome, welcome to
请坐，大家请坐
Sit down, everybody sit down
家父有意安排两位吃餐便饭
My father would like to arrange two eating Pa potluck
是想叫俩位互相了解一下
Wants to make two know each other a T
教堂重不重开，其实并不重要
Church is not heavy to open, does not really matter
主要是我们要实行民主，实行多教
The main thing we want to practice democracy, the implementation of multi-teach
我相信在座的贤能父老都 是这个意思，对不对？
I believe that is the meaning of the elite crowd, right?
对
To
蛮好的嘛，有头有脸的都来了
Well fine, have a head have come face
来来来，边吃边聊
Come, come, drink and chat
大家不要客气
We do not mention it
其实，中国的道教就像北京烤鸭一样
In fact, China's Taoism as Beijing roast duck
有着上千年的历史，中 国人吃起来头头是道
Has a history of thousands of years, Chinese people eat good choices
外国人吃起来就不懂了
Foreigners do not understand to eat
中国的宗教，好处就是劝人向善
Chinese religion, the advantage is advising people to perform good deeds
坏处就是导人迷信
The downside is that leaders superstition
其实信仰就跟吃烤鸭一样
In fact, the same beliefs just eat roast duck
只要能够把它吃下了肚
As long as it is able to eat the belly
至于怎么吃，不成问题
As for how to eat, not a problem
想不到神父懂得这样吃烤鸭
Think of the priest who has learned that eating roast duck
事实证明，得罪了祖 师爷，小心把你噎死
Facts have proved that offended the patron deity, accidentally choke you
什么叫祖师爷？
What is the patron deity?
神师爷，Grand Father
God adviser, Grand Father
原来你祖师爷还健在，替我问候他
So you ancestral still alive for me to greet him
好，我问候你娘亲
Well, I greet you Niangqin
谢谢，谢谢，
Thank you, thank you, I respect you
来，大家喝酒，来
Come, we drink, to
这种酒呢，是神父从法兰西带回来的
This wine it is the priest brought back from France
叫做白兰地
Called brandy
阿星
A Star
我师父不喜欢喝这种 酒，他喜欢喝这种
My teacher does not like to drink this wine, he drank this Tonghuan
九叔，我们言归正传
Jiushu, we get down to business
希望吃完这顿饭，以 后大家和和气气的
I hope eating this meal, after we harmoniously
对，和气生财
Right, harmoniously
和气生财我不反对
I am not against making money and gas
但是，你不要指望我 会跟他们狼狈为奸
However, you do not expect me to act in collusion with them
什么叫狼狈为奸
What is hand in glove
你难道真的不知道 他们是什么人吗？
You really do not know what people do?
当然知道，说给九叔听
Of course, know that listening to Jiushu
他们是
They are
他们不是开烟馆，就是开妓院
They are not open dens, is to open a brothel
根本没有一个好人
There is no a good man
无所谓的，说给九叔听
Does not matter, said knot Jiushu listen
因为，他们是
Because they are
不用说了，又是神爱世人那一套
Needless to say, it was God so loved the world that set
九叔，你学得还真快啊
Jiushu, you really learn how fast
你们神爱世人，难道也爱坏人吗
Your God so loved the world, do not you love the bad guys
在座的没有坏人
No bad people here
说给九叔听，他们是什么人
Say to Jiushu listen, they are what people
他们是罪人
They are sinners
各位，既然志不同，道不合
Ladies and gentlemen, since the annals different channel sub-
你们要重开教堂，我 也没办法，MY son !
You want to re-open the church, I have no idea, My son!
师父
Master
告诉他们听
Tell them to listen
说什么
Say what
我们走啊
走啊
Walked
愿万能的主宽恕他们，阿门
May Almighty God forgive them, Amen
小月
Satsuki
师父睡觉了，我们去喝茶
Master bed, we drink tea
好啊
Well
早啊，九叔，你也到教堂去听经啊
Early. Ah, Jiushu, you can also listen to the church by ah
我不会去的
I will not go
那我走先了
Then I go first, the
对不起，小姐，请点圣水
Excuse me, miss, please holy water
因父，及子及圣神之名者，阿门
Father, Son and Holy Spirit in the name of those who, Amen
你好
Hello
大叔，欢迎你，谢谢
Uncle, you are welcome, thank you
弥撒就快开始了吧
Mass start it soon
对呀，马上就开始了
Yes, immediately began
我想神父今天一定很 高兴，来那么多人
I think the priest must be very happy today to so many people
师兄，你干嘛不去当修士？
Brother, why do you go when the monks?
你吃错药了？
You are eating you up?
老太太，欢迎，欢迎
Lady, welcome, welcome
老太太，请点圣水
Lady, please holy water
一定要点？
Fixed point?
不是这样
Not so
没事找事做，自己找麻烦，笨鸟
Nothing good to do yourself in trouble, stupid black
老太太，老太太，你怎么了
Old lady, old lady, how do you
让我来，让我来
Let me, let me
阿婆，你没事吧
Lady, are you okay
没事，没事
Set things right
扶这位老太太进去坐吧
Help the old lady go sit down
好，阿婆，这边请
Well, lady, this way please
真难得哦
Oh really rare
这么大年纪，还能接受西方的文化
So much older, but also to accept Western culture
我来凑一下热闹
I'll join in the fun look
我知道了，阿婆，你一 定把这当成庙会了
I know, lady, you set this as a temple
那也好过我们的师父
That is better than our master
你师父怎么了
Your teacher how the
我们师父食古不化，就像老顽固
Our Master pedantic, like old fogy
对啊对啊，如果被他知道我们来教堂
Ah right ah, if he knew we were coming church
他一定会把我们的腿打断的
He definitely put our legs interrupted
阿婆，你怎么了
Lady, how do you
我走不了
I could not walk
我们架着你走，来
We hobble you go to
小心
Careful
不好意思
Feel embarrassed
Anny，我陪你一起坐
Anny, I'll sit with you
神父，一切都准备好了
Father, everything is ready
上主，我一心仰望你， 我依靠你便不会蒙羞
Lord, I look up to you and I wholeheartedly rely on you will not be ashamed
不要让我的仇人向我夸耀
Do not let my enemies rejoice over me
凡祈望你的人却不致失望
Where people have hope you will not be disappointed
因父，及子及圣神之名者，阿门
Father, Son and Holy Spirit in the name of those who, Amen
开门
Open
愿天父的慈爱，圣宠，圣 神的恩赐，与你们同在
May the Father's love, grace, the gift of the Holy Spirit, be with you in
也与你的心同在
But also with your heart with the
最仁慈的圣父，我们仰赖你的圣子
Most merciful Father, we rely on your Son
我们的主，恳求你悦纳降
Our Lord, beseech you accept drop. . .
这位老太太，请你到台上来
The old lady, would you please come to the stage
恳求主悦纳降服于你
Ask the Lord accept surrender to you
开口，开口呀
Opening, opening it
阿门
Amen
张开嘴
Open your mouth
你有什么感觉？
Do you have any sense of the party?
没味道
No taste
我是问你对神的感受
I was asking you about God's feelings
那我再吃多一块
I eat more than one
好，愿主赐福给你
Well, may the Lord bless you
我现在有点感受了， 你又感觉怎么样？
I now feel a little sense of the party and how about you?
好痛啊
Good disease ah
你也会觉得痛啊
You will feel really hurt
上主饶恕你，我不能饶恕你
Lord forgive you, I can not forgive you
你不饶恕我？你重开 教堂，我还不饶恕你
Do not you forgive me? You reopen the church, I do not forgive you
你重开教堂，我还不饶恕你
You reopen the church, I do not forgive you
你怎么打神父啊
You how Dayou father. A
别生气，别生气，交给我来对付
Do not be angry, do not be angry, to me to deal with
女人生气，好容易老的
Woman angry, with great difficulty old
师...
Division. . .
兔崽子
Bastard
师父，是你啊
Master, are you ah
你不要出声，要不师父没面子
You do not say anything, or master hair face
现在怎么收场？
Now how end?
你还敢给我跑？你跑啊你
You dare to give me a run? You ran and you
你敢吃老娘豆腐？
You dare to eat tofu aging mother?
师兄，师兄
Brother, Brother
师父，你好狠啊
Master, you Haohen. A
狠的还在后头哪，回去
Which ruthless yet to come, to go back
湘西赶尸，生人回避
Xiangxi Vampire, avoiding strangers
快点，发生什么事了？
Come on, what happened?
王修士暴毙了
Wangxiu Shi died suddenly of
那我们进去看看
Then we go in and see
死人了，师父
Dead, Master
师父，那个修士
Master, the monks
看起来很麻烦
Looks like a lot of trouble
为什么？
Why?
这教堂不干净
This church is not clean
不会吧，他们全都粉刷过了
Oh, no, they were all painted up
我不是说这个
I am not saying that this
有鬼？
Ghosts?
主啊，求你仁慈垂引我们的祈祷
Lord ah, I beg you to pray our merciful hanging cited
使我们坚信你的圣子从死者中复活
Make us believe in your Son from the dead
乾坤罗移
Move heaven and earth Romania
主说，就是他交给我的 ，要我一个都不失掉
Lord said that he entrusted to me, asking me to not lose a
而且在末日，还要使他们复活
And in the end, but also so that they resurrected
我主降服的人们，你们来吧
My lord surrender people, you come
因父，及子及圣神之名者，阿门
Father, Son and Holy Spirit in the name of those who, Amen
求你减轻我心中的痛苦
I pray thee, tell alleviate pain in my heart
请你消除我一切的烦恼
Please remove all my troubles
定，啊，败北
Be, ah, defeat
主啊，请你保护我
Lord ah, please protect me
拯救我，别让我蒙羞
Save me, do not let me be ashamed
金刚印，伏魔咒
Diamond India, volts curse
拯救灵魂，远离撒旦
Salvation of souls, away from Satan
师父，这鬼好厉害哦
Master, this ghost Li official oh well
废话
Nonsense
拯救灵魂，远离撒旦
Salvation of souls, away from Satan
请主赐我力量
Please God give me strength
师父，真有你的
Master, you really have
没两下子，怎么做你师父
No two Now, how do you master
神父，终于把他制服了
Priest, and finally subdued him
因父、及子及圣神之名者，阿门
Father, Son and Holy Spirit in the name of those who, Amen
师父
Master
打得好，连你都认不出 我来，说明我扮得很像
Set well, even you did not recognize me, that I play very like
你干嘛要扮成这样？
Organs to pretend like you do?
我们去偷尸
We steal the corpse
搞什么鬼，走啊
What the hell, walked
你想把教堂烧了？
You want to burn the church?
那怎么办？
How to do?
搬他走
He moved away
你们想放火烧教堂？
You want to set fire to the church?
你不要阻止我们烧尸
Do not stop us from burning the corpse
神父
Fr
你们放火？
You fire?
你们想干什么？放开我，放开我
What do you want? Let me go, let me go
师父
Master
湘西赶尸，生人回避
Xiangxi Vampire, avoiding strangers
师父，吃面了
Master, eat noodles
对不起，神父
I'm sorry, Father
如果我没闻错的话，你 师父的排泄物它告诉我
If I did not hear you correctly, you master it tells me excreta
他得了重感冒，我来替他看病
He has a bad flu and I back him to see a doctor
里边请，请请请
Inside, please, please please please
来，坐下，坐下
, Sit down, sit down
这里是你家还是我家？
Here is your place or mine?
一样一样
Much the same as
My son , come on . come on
My son, Come on, Come on
干什么？
What?
给你看病
Results you see a doctor
看病？我像有病吗？
Doctor? I like it?
中国有句俗语，病向浅中医
Chinese saying goes, disease early diagnosis
感目虽然是很普通的病
Although it is very common sense Chang disease
可是感昌严重的话，也会转成肺炎
But the flu and serious, it will turn into pneumonia
肺炎如果严重的话，就会致命啊
Pneumonia if severe, can be fatal ah
哦，你特别来咒我死啊
Oh, you especially to curse me Sia
不不不
No, no
师父，神父是来帮你的
Master, the priest is here to help you
不必了
Do not have a
师父，你让我们开开眼界嘛
Master, you let us eye-opener Well
我还没见过洋人怎么给人治病耶
I have not seen how people treat foreigners yeah
你拿师父当实验品啊
You take the master as guinea pigs ah
老小子，真有你的
Old boy, you really have
我先给你打一针，控制病情
I would let you set a pin to control the disease
然后吃颗阿斯匹灵， 睡个觉，就没事了
Then eat pieces of aspirin a nap, all right
你们俩都听到了
Both of you have heard
他不但要拿针来扎我 还要拿什么安非他命给我吃
He not only bring the needle to tie knot I would take what amphetamines begging me 0
你来探病，我多谢你
You come to visit the sick, and I thank you
看病就不用了，有病我自己会看
Doctor would not, I would look sick
你别嘴硬，相信我
Do not fooling you, believe me
信你？信你死得快
Believe you? Believe you died quickly
拿家伙
Take guy
师父，这招没教过我
Master, this move did not teach me
我是唬他的，拿水来啊
I'm a fool him, brought water to ah
天灵灵，地灵灵， 湘西赶尸，生人回避
Day Lingling Lingling, Hunan Vampire, avoiding strangers
别捅篓子
Do not poke baskets
湘西赶尸，生人回避
Xiangxi Vampire, avoiding strangers
爹地，这次计划顺利的 话，我们可以发大财了
Daddy, this plan goes well, we can fortunes
教堂一开，九叔那个老家伙
Church opened, Jiushu old guy
就算赶不走他，他也威信全无
Even expel him, and he prestige throughout the day
以后他再说什么，都没有人信了
Later he say anything, no one believed
相不到这次这么容易搞定
This phase can not be so easy to get
叶镇长，那些货我已经
Ye Zhenchang those goods I have
他是谁？
Who is he?
我是他儿子
I was his son
那么大家是自己人嘛
Then everyone one of us shun
叶镇长，以前我怎么求 你，你就是不肯答应
Yezhen Chang, before I ask you how you refused to agree
这一次怎么突然改变主意了
This time, how suddenly changed his mind
这是我的主意，你来 的目的是拿钱吧？
This is my idea, you come to the purpose of money, right?
爹地，你照我的话告诉他
Daddy, you told him as I say
你的意思是怎么样？
Do you mean is how?
我的意思，货我已经给你送到了
I mean, I have the goods sent to you knot
我的兄弟等着钱用啊
My brother waiting for money ah
都已经给你很多方便 了，你算便宜一点
You have to make a lot of parties, you little less
八折，好不好，好不好啊
Discount for each purchase, okay, okay 0 A
人最怕不知有口臭
I wonder if people are most afraid of bad breath
今晚，非常荣幸能够邀 请到你与我共进晚餐
Tonight, very honored to have you and I together late Pa
自从上次在酒楼遇到你之后
Since the last time you met in a restaurant after
你的影子就深深地留在我脑海里
Your shadow will remain deep in my mind
Anny，我喜欢你，我爱你
Anny, I love you, I love you
来，用餐吧
Come, dining bar
谁啊，半夜三更敲门， 吵死了，来了来了
Who, noisy dead midnight knock on the door, come come
啊，是她？
Ah, yes she?
Anny小姐， 是什么风把你给吹来啦？
Miss Anny, is what brings you here now?
是不是来找我？
Is not come to me?
你要我站在门口跟你说话啊？
You want me standing in the doorway talking to you ah?
不不不，这边请，不，这边，这边
No, no way, please, no, here, here
不对，你先请
No, you first call
请坐，师妹，倒茶，有客人叫
Sit down, junior sister apprentice, tea, there are noisy guests
请坐，请坐
Sit down, sit down
你师父九叔呢？
Your master Jiushu it?
我师父喝酒去了 有什么事，跟我说也是一样
My master went there anything to drink, told me that the same
这样，我有件事想请教九叔
So, I would like to ask one thing Jiushu
哦，请说
Oh, please say
我觉得晚上那个赶尸 的，有点不对劲耶
I think that the corpse of the night, something is wrong yeah
有这种事情？
There is such a thing?
你才不对劲，你来干嘛？
You just wrong, are you doing here?
Anny是来找师父的
Anny am looking for Master's
师父不会的，我都会
Master will not, I will
不不，师父会的，我都会
No, no, Master will, I will
有什么困难，说给我听，一切OK
What is so difficult that knot me, O drop everything
僵尸有没有灵性啊？
Zombies have no spiritual ah?
僵尸是人死之后的一个躯壳
Zombies are dead after a shell
连人性都没有，何来灵性呢？
Are not even human, how spiritual it?
我怀疑他们时面一定有内情
I suspect they must have inside information when the surface
好，我陪你去看看
Well, I go to see
好呀
Okay
你这个人真没有理性
You people really no reason
你不要听他胡说，到 时候真的遇上僵尸
Do not listen to him, when the time is really encounter zombies
连他都自身难保，到时候，你
Even he was unable to help themselves, to the time you
好，为了你的安全，你先回家
Well, for your safety, you can go home
好啊，那我们一起去
Well, then we went to
我有说过跟你一起去吗
Did I say you go with you
好吧，那我先回去了， 你自己小心一点哦
Well, I go back, you be careful, oh
好好，谢谢
Well, thank you
准备家伙
Preparation guy
该还钱了，不然不玩了
The pay back the money, or do not play
他妈的，急什么急，等跑 完这一趟就还给你了
Damn, what urgent urgent, and so on back to finish this trip you up
想不到现在带毒品进 出酒泉镇这么容易耶
She now took goods out of town so easy yeah Jiuquan
镇上教堂能够重开啊
Town church to reopen ah
就表示镇长已经把镇民给控制住了
Says the mayor has put the town of China knot under control
有人来了，快
It was coming,
没什么不对啊
Let nothing wrong. A
是假的
Is false
是吗？试了就知道
Is that right? Try it out for yourself
师妹，你记不记得师父说过 遇到僵尸该怎么对付？
Junior sister apprentice, Master said, do you remember how to deal with the encounter zombies?
记得，师父说，只要口念降尸咒
Remember, the master said, as long as I read down the corpse curse
僵尸就会受你控制了
Zombies will be under your control
好，让我试试
Well, let me try
一请悟空降阳降
Please. Tang Yang airborne drop
二请孙猴显灵通
Two monkeys were informed please SUN
三请大圣耀威风
Please Story Yao prestige
急急如律令，僵尸听令
Hastily as law to defend, zombie listen up
挺
Very
脚跳
Foot jump
头摇
Head pinch
屁股翘
Alice ass
天地无极，乾坤借法，起
Promise heaven, heaven and earth, by law, from the
谁叫你们来此地的？
Why did you come here for?
如果尸变，你们担当得起吗？
If Evil Dead, you afford it?
道长，这些尸能变吗？
A head, you can change these dead?
此地的事，你们最好少管，滚
Here things and you best little tube, roll
是
Be
如果你们敢再乱动， 当心我要你们的命
If you dare to tamper with the life I want you to be careful
走，我们回去告诉师父
Go, we go back and tell Master
师父，师父，不得了了，想也想不到
Master, Master, incredible, could not conceive
什么事
What
教堂后院停的尸
Church backyard dead stop
他怎么会在这里呢
How could he do here
神秘兮兮的，搞什么鬼？
Today's mystery today, What the hell?
这两位是我徒弟，这位是屠龙道长
This two are my disciples, this is a long road Dragonslayer
道长
Long Road
好，你可真有福气啊
Well, you may be lucky ah Room
我看你们俩位都是聪明人，对不对
I see your previous two are smart people, right
没事的时候，常待在 家里跟师父学点功夫
Nothing, I often stay at home with the master learn kung fu
不要成天的在外面乱 跑，很容易闯祸的
Do not run around all day long on the outside, it is easy to get into trouble
我这两个徒弟就是不成材啊
I have these two disciples is shape up. A
师父，不是，他
Master, not, he
我们是同门，我知道你的底
We are the same door, I know your bottom
你不做伤天害理的事
You do not do wicked things
这一次纯粹路过，我希望你能
This is a pure passing, I hope you can
你赶你的尸，只要不借尸还魂就行了
You catch your corpse, they do not reincarnated on the line
师父，他不只赶尸，他还
Master, he not only corpse, he also
他是借尸运毒
He was dead by drug trafficking
屠龙，你又在干什么坏事？
Dragon, you're doing something ring?
你以为你以前做过的就是好事吗
You think you've done a good thing it is
师父
Master
好，今天你们人多，有 机会我会再回来的
Well, many people today you have the chance I'll be back again
师父，你以前
Master, you've
干什么？
What?
兔崽子，跑哪去了？
Bastard, where to run?
谁呀？
Who?
救命啊，救命啊
Help ah, help ah
救命啊
Help ah
有僵尸啊，有僵尸啊
There are zombies, ah, ah zombie
救命啊
Help ah
爹地，你做什么啊
Daddy, what you do ah
怎么这样啊，你梦游啊
How so ah, ah you sleepwalking
有僵尸
There are zombies
哪有僵尸啊，我又没看 到，你不要这么紧张嘛
How can zombies ah, I did not see that you will not be so nervous Well
有僵尸啊
There zombie ah
没有啦，你先坐下，休息一下
Not really, sit down, take a break
爹地
Daddy
爹地，你血多，你上啊
Daddy, you blood, you go ah
他怕大蒜啊
He was afraid of garlic ah
爹地，上啊
Daddy, on the ah
你现在知道吃大蒜的好处了吧
So now you know the benefits of eating garlic bar
他怕佛像啊
He was afraid Buddha ah
对，来
Right, to
钱我会给你
I will end you residual
求求你不要这样对付 我，你帮我制服他
I beg you not to do this to me, you help me subdue him
来来来
Come
凡事好商量
Everything good discussion
钱呢，我们一定会给 ，我给你出个主意
Preserves it, we will give, I bear thee counsel
我这个主意怎么样？你发什么呆嘛
I like the idea how? Well you're staring
我的眼镜呢
My glasses it
找到了
Found
最近镇上发生了好多古怪事
Recently a lot of weird things happen in town
不知道九叔你这里
Here you do not know Jiushu
道观重地，任何脏东西不敢来
Taoist powerhouse, afraid to come any nasties
对，就跟教堂一样， 也不会发生什么事
Right, just as the church, it will not happen
九叔，你上回烧的那个
Jiushu you burn on the back of that
符吗？
Character do?
符，是不是真的可以驱魔治病？
Character, is not really possible exorcism cure?
这个跟信上帝一样，只 要你诚心的话就会灵
This with believe in God, as long as you sincerely, they would have the Spirit
有什么困难，尽管说
What is so difficult, though, said
没有没有，我是说
No, I mean,
如果教堂里面也贴了符，笑死人了
If the inside of the church also posted a character, laughable people
九叔，时间不早了，我要回去了
Jiushu, the hour is late, I want to go back
我们走
是，神父
Yes, Father
神父，你相信会有用吗
Father, do you believe will be useful
我恐怕我控制不了自己，希望它有效
I am afraid that I can not control myself, I hope it effectively
神会答应这样做吗？
God promised to do this?
神会谅解的
God will understand the
是你啊，来找我师父？
Are you, ah, come my master?
他刚出去了，很快会 回来的，到里头等
He just went out, and soon will be back to the inside, etc.
你倒是进来坐啊
You'd come in and sit ah
你来做什么？
What do you want?
进来说，等我师父回来了
Came in and said, so I came back master
你再将你师父的坏事讲给他听好了
You then tell your teacher's bad guitar listen up
你这样跳，累不累啊
You do jump, tired ah
不要再装了，谁不晓 得你是假装僵尸啊
Do not re-installed, you do not know who is pretending zombie ah
师兄，师兄，是真的耶
Brother, brother, really yeah
什么真的？
What Really?
师兄，你这次真的引鬼入室了
Brother, you cited this really a ghost burglary
我怎么知道他是真僵尸啊
How do I know that he is a self-zombie ah
卡住了
Stuck
师兄，还不快去拿家伙，快呀
Brother, do not go and take the guy, Come
师兄，你没事吧？
Brother, are you okay?
你搞什么鬼啊
What are you up ah
师父，里面大件事啊
Master, which is a big deal ah
拿符来
Take breaks to
到底教堂有多少僵尸
In the end how many zombies Church
大概有八个假的 不过现在可能已经变成真的僵尸了
About eight fake but now may have become really a zombie
这下麻烦大了
This is the next big trouble
那怎么办，师父
How to do that, Master
得找那个老怪师谈一下
Teachers may find that odd to talk about
谁是老怪物啊？
Who is the old monster ah?
就是那个神父啊
Is that the priest ah
神父，神父
Priest, Fr
不要过来
Do not come
九叔来找你
Jiushu come to you
我快控制不住了，解决我
I am almost unable to control, the solution I
不
Not
角军决我
Solution I
不
Not
我求你，解决我
I beg you, to solve my
不
Not
我求你，你回来，不要走
I beg you, you come back, do not go
九叔，神父他
Jiushu, the priest he
九叔，快点救我，我快不行了
Jiushu, hurry, help me, I will never die
神父
Fr
谢谢你，这只能解决一时的痛苦
Thank you, this is only a temporary solution to the pain report
罪恶之源在下面，我带你们去
Source of evil in the following, I take you to
怎么不见了？
How missing?
魔鬼
Devil
撒法网
Caesar Roland Garros
怎么会这样
How could this
师父，用狗血淋他
Master, with his dog discredited
外国僵尸溅到血，会更厉害的
Foreign zombie spilled blood, would be more vigorous Palace
还好没事
Fortunately nothing
师父
Master
用桃木剑
With Tao Mujian
师父，剑都没了，怎么办？
Master Sword is gone, how do?
你去引开他
You go to distract him
去
Go
师兄，你没事吧？
Brother, are you okay?
好像没事
If nothing
师父
Master
这到底是什么鬼，怎么什么都不怕？
This in the end is what the hell, how afraid of anything?
洋鬼
Foreign devil
师父，你保重
Master, you take care of yourself
你懂洋文，快点搞定那个洋鬼
Do you understand foreign language, hurry up to get the foreign devil
十字架
Cross
魔鬼
Devil
上帝会惩罚你
God will punish you
神父
Fr
求你放过神父，不要再害人了
Let thy priests, not to Husband of
快去帮他
Go and help him
夺命招魂伞
Evocation deadly umbrella
阿星让开
A star so open
星哥，你摔伤了没有？
Star brother, you hurt yourself?
我没事
I'm fine.
给我看一下
Junction me look
师父
Master
阿星，接剑
A star, then the sword
天主降魔
God fell monsters
天师显灵
Fearless apparitions
中西合壁
Western wall units
天下无敌
Invincible
阿星，替神父祈祷
A star, pray for priests